Previously on Zombieland Saga Revenge, the top idol group Iron Frill came to our town!
They'll be packing seats with fans for sure!
I still can't believe we were picked to be their opening act at Saga Arena!
Kotaro isn't taking chances and is keeping Ai from performing,
so no one recognizes her as Iron Frill's original leader!
Meanwhile, Ai's been doing solo gigs while we prepare for the concert.
Frontier Street feels weird without her.
We can't mess up again like we did at the EFS! The anxiety is real!
To make matters worse, Iron Frill's new leader, Shiori, tried to get Ai to join their group!
We won't let that happen, no matter what!
Listen up, number three. You should join Iron Frill.
Everything's just fine. Ai is not going to abandon us,
and she's not gonna join those girls in Iron Frill.
I mean, aside from the whole being a zombie thing, she's a part of our group.
One of us.
I sure hope you're right about that.
If she were here, she'd probably yell at me for being so nervous about the show.
No kidding! I would be in full-on rage mode about it.
She's like,
I don't want to hear that kind of talk. Stop worrying and zombie up!
We shouldn't tell the other girls about what we just saw. It would only worry them.
After all, the Saga Arena show is coming up fast.
And we're gonna rock it!
We're gonna rock it!
We'll rock it!
That was sick
You're really bringing it, Tai
We've totally got this show in the bag
Junko?
Are you in there?
You okay?
You look a little wobbly
Huh?
What's wrong?
I thought we were doing a better job
Or maybe you just need a calming nap?
I'm fine, really
Sorry about that
I'm just gonna step outside for a minute
And get some fresh air
So, that was weird
She's been acting strange lately
Have you guys noticed?
I wonder what's up
Junko must be going through something rough
Ever since Ai started doing solo performances
She had the super haunted look in her eyes
Well, that new arena ain't gonna rock itself
Hear me?
Let's crank this mother to 11
Right
Junko must still be super worried about Ai leaving the group
I wish there was something I could do
Maybe I could go ask Ai
Man, this sucks
What am I gonna do?
It smells so good
One of the customers from the bar last night offered us a ton of food
And it's everything Junko loves, too
Ooh, is that beef?
Yes, but it's reserved for Ai's packed lunch today
Oh, yeah
I forgot that she's recording solo tonight
One should never enter a battle on an empty stomach
If the body's not strong, then the mind will shut down
And if all else fails, remember to smile
You can count on me for lunch help
Would you mind setting the table for me?
Make sure that I get some rice in her lunchbox as well
Mm-hmm
That rice scoop is around here somewhere
Yeah, that looks great
Spots are all set
Coming through
Right
Check the balls
Would you just look at this?
We'll go over our routines once everyone is ready
Huh?
We have to put on our best show tonight
Then she'll finally see how strong we are
Hmm
Shiori
Got a sec?
What's up, Yui?
I heard you tried to recruit a new member to the team
Without talking to the rest of us in advance
Someone from that local saga group with the weird name
Yes, I did
She might be working in obscurity out here
But don't doubt her skills for a second
Just think how much stronger we'd be
If we had more talent to add to our shows
Iron Frill has to continue evolving
That's what makes us top idols
That's not the problem, Shiori
I'm worried about you
What'd I do?
I know you want her to join us
But haven't you noticed the resemblance?
She's like I'm Mizuno's twin
Sure, she was legendary
The best center we ever had
Her name will forever be attached to Iron Frill
And for good reason
I know that I'm Mizuno was a big deal once
Before
But we've moved on
Look, I want her to join Iron Frill
Because I can see her potential
I have no other motive behind doing it
Okay, girls
Let's run through the whole set
Where does I belong?
What if she's better off with Iron Frill?
Junko?
Why are you sitting out here all by yourself?
Don't you have practice?
I should get back
Is everything okay?
I'm fine
I just needed to take a break
It's nothing to worry about
Wait, was there a fight or something?
No, it's nothing like that
I know you have another solo gig coming up
So don't worry about us
You should focus on your own thing
Something is wrong
Please talk to me
Okay, fine
Did you like being the center of Iron Frill
More than being in Franshushu?
And tell me the truth
Seriously?
You're out here worrying about me
At a crucial time like this?
You have to let that question go
Before you get everyone else upset
Do you want another EFS disaster on your hands?
But you didn't say no
You didn't answer my question
Hey, what's up, Ai?
Welcome back
Was Junko out there with you?
Dinner's almost ready
So we should probably tell her
Did she just give me the brush off?
She probably didn't hear me
Yeah, that's it
Why, Ai?
Why are you so stupid?
Hey there, lonely girl
I thought I was the only one
That cried on this beach
Did you get your heart broken
Or something like that?
I've been there myself a few times
Love's a real bummer
I can't even count how often
I've been rejected
I just keep on falling
For the wrong kind of lady
I got you, Boo
Oh dang, you're kind of young, huh?
Sorry about that
I shouldn't be out here
Chatting up someone so
обоappled
Marte
Thank you, Sakura.
What is it, sneaky pants?
I was just...
Are you girls prepared for the show?
Yeah, I guess.
But I might leave the group and join Iron Frill!
Their leader, Shiori, is trying to recruit her.
She had the nerve to tell Ai that Franz Shushu wasn't good enough for her.
I don't know what we'd do without her with us.
And yet at the same time, I think Ai is more talented than we are.
Blah, blah, blah, Franz Shushu isn't good enough for Ai.
This isn't about her, baby.
This is actually about you!
A member's gonna pack and leave, and you're totes cool with her bailing?
You mean you're just gonna sit by and let that happen?
Can you accept that?
You're some kind of chump!
Yeah!
Cause that's what it sounds like you're saying to me!
That you're a loser who can't hack it in the big leagues!
You can't even stop your friends from leaving!
Poor Jugko letting the world slip through her stupid fingers!
While I think that is pathetic!
Nobody wants to follow a failure who doesn't believe in herself!
You gotta shine, sister!
Go on. Shred it.
I've taken this axe into battle my whole life.
With every kick-ass, my soul comes alive, rises from the ashes like a damned phoenix!
If this mamacita keeps making sweet music, then I can greet another day.
When people stand in my way, rock blocking me with logic and rules,
I just take up my weapon and thrash that trash!
That's my sweet mantra!
And it's also why I'm literally never upset!
Yeah, but I thought that you were super depressed just the other day.
Baby, listen to your soul!
That thing's crying out to you to smash it!
And shred it!
Shred those excuses, smash that like button, and subscribe to rock!
Don't limit yourself to one lane!
If there's something that you want in this life, then rise up and take what's yours!
You might be undead, but you've still got a light inside you!
Shine bright and the world will follow!
Blow that to bits!
You're Junko Kono!
You're back!
Finally!
I can't wait that long to eat!
Right!
Thank you for this food!
Listen up, everyone!
I have a new plan for the Saga Arena!
Huh?
Thanks for the food!
Junko, would you like to try some of this?
So good!
Thank you!
Thank you for this food!
Junko, would you like to try some of this?
So good!
Thanks for the food!
Junko, would you like to try some of this?
So good!
Thanks for the food!
Junko, would you like to try some of this?
So good!
It's the first time!
The good time!
You sure?
How are you thinking?
Uh…
You were too late.
Wow, I'm impressed. Kotaro has a magic touch with liquid liner wings and contouring cheekbones.
I think he might have watched a bunch of online tutorials.
See? Yeah, he has the technique down, cause I can't manage to nail that hey I'm not dead look.
No! Tai, the tour bus is not a drum set!
You're done baking. Now get on out there and smash it!
Yeah!
Are you kidding me? You're not gonna perform tonight?
Well, that's just how everything worked out. Anyway, I thought you should know.
The only reason we came here was so that you could see how amazing we are!
Franshushu is just a bunch of losers without you. You're making a huge mistake!
You shouldn't underestimate Franshushu.
They've been getting better every day. And even I should try harder if I'm gonna stay in the group. Watch them perform. You'll see what I'm talking about.
This had better be something.
Hey, do you know who's opening?
Oh, you know them. Those local girls who bombed at the EFS.
Yeah, I saw that online. I hope they do better this time.
I'm getting nervous for Franshushu. This venue's a pretty big deal.
On top of that, it's enemy territory.
All this time, you never actually worried that anyone was going to recognize me, right Kotaro?
I think against that...
Marion Howe did we start a stream?
Wige.
I was gonna try to.
Just make sure to drink, please let yourselves of your999'12 cast.
I felt for a reason carefully.
Mmm...
I said it wouldn't want to change ya, too.
I'd love to change, too.
I saw the distance from the top of this.
Yeah, this is the right banger!
Smash it, Shuko!
Easy it's my way!
突き果てて
天心 wake up!
Just like this!
Ready!
1, 2
伸ばせ!
Ready!
2, 2
暮れるまで get down!
激しく高ぶな気持ち
花火を断むがさない
夢を超えて
With classicagine
Adie
Yeah
To be brave, so never fly
Just do it,手にするまでは
Yeah, to be brave, so never fly
Let's take it,掲げろ, have some
Just do it,手にするまで
Some fight
Oh
Watch the limbs, dummy.
Sorry, I forgot.
Oh my gosh, are you okay?
Yeah, we're fine.
Because we're already dead.
You've still got a light inside you.
Shine bright and the world will follow.
Lighter Light Show!
Loaded Light Show!
Love 1.
I lost love
What kind of special effects are they using exactly?
What kind of special effects are they using?
You girls did great out there.
I have to be honest, I wasn't expecting anything at that level from you.
But now you're going to see a real performance.
I'd pay attention if I were you.
We'll show you where you belong.
Hey!
Number three is a member of our group, and she's not going anywhere.
We don't need her.
Our special guests today are the girls from Tokyo's very own Iron Frill.
Welcome!
Thank you so much for having us on!
I hate to admit it, but they really were amazing.
It's more than evident how they achieved their fame.
I don't care how famous they are.
When we take over the country, we've got a score to settle with those chicks.
I'll eat them alive!
In the meantime, we're going to work extra hard to level up our skills!
Yeah!
While performing solo, I was able to get an outside perspective about Fron Shushu.
It might give us a clear direction moving forward.
Thanks, Sai.
Any input would be great to hear from you.
You had to pick one thing.
What was the most memorable part of this tour?
Wow, let me think.
Fron Shushu was incredible.
Fron Shuu?
I think that group is probably our biggest competition.
They might even be our rivals.
We're rivals?
They might grow to be the same.
They they can be agents.
We're blonde from the other people
perhaps even ours.
We're gonna eventually马峰,
they might be the one.
They might be the only ones that we might be taken of
our haha.
So, what would they take over the past?
As I was wondering,
do these things...
They might go ahead.
Thank you so much.
他们 would be some good ones.
They might be the next time.
It's not always good to somebody.
So, there's enoughunes.
There may be some pneumonia.
That will still hook you up.
They might be the very fun in the field.